housecarers.com 2017-02-02

# HouseCarers House Sitting privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**  
  
INTRODUCTION 

HouseCarers.com understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide information about yourself in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at HouseCarers.com more valuable to you. We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information HouseCarers.com may collect, how such information may be used, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use (the "TCU") posted on the Site. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the TCU.   

_The Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of eighteen._ Individuals who are under the age of eighteen are expressly prohibited from submitting to HouseCarers.com or posting to the Site any personally identifiable information about themselves.   

By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in Australia, the United States,  and/or any other country.   

**This Privacy Policy explains: **  
  
| 

what personally identifiable information HouseCarers.com collects from you, and how HouseCarers.com uses the information;  
with whom your information may be shared;  
what choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information;  
what cookies are, and how HouseCarers.com uses them;  
how HouseCarers.com protects your personal information;   
how you can access, update or delete your information;  
what else you should know about your online privacy; and  
how you can contact us

 **1. What personally identifiable information HouseCarers.com collects from you, and how HouseCarers.com uses the information.**  
  
HouseCarers.com collects and stores personal information in several ways at different parts of our Site. This information may include your legal name, email address, age, gender, User ID, User Password. We collect this information in order to provide you with our services more easily, and in a more personalized manner. HouseCarers will not individually identify any user to a third part except when required to do so under the law and under the special circumstances specified under with whom your information may be shared;

| 

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network  privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

---  
  
**2. With whom your information may be shared.**  
  
HouseCarers.com will not sell, rent or barter your personal information. However, we may from time to time aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, traffic patterns and site usage. Such aggregate information will not individually identify any user.

We reserve the right to disclose any information if such action is necessary (a) to conform to the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process or subpoena served on HouseCarers.com, (b) to protect and defend the legal rights or property of HouseCarers.com, the Site, or its users, or (c) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of its users or the general public. We further reserve the right to release any information concerning any user if that user participates (or is reasonably suspected of participating) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution.   
  
**3. What choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information.**  
  
You may occasionally receive information about HouseCarers.com services. HouseCarers.com believes that these updates are interesting and informative You may subsequently contact us to request to be removed from this list. In every update that we send, we will include an option to discontinue receipt of future updates. HouseCarers.com reserves the right to limit any registrations on our Site to those who will accept our information and to those who will provide the requested information.   

 **4. What cookies are, and how HouseCarers.com uses them. **  
  
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, HouseCarers.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. All portions of the Site that prompt you to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. No other company has access to cookies placed on your computer by HouseCarers.com. We may use cookies technology to reduce the time required for you to submit your requests and for HouseCarers.com to respond to such requests. Cookies will not be used by us to retrieve any information about you, or from your computer,that you have not voluntarily given to us. Cookies placed on your computer by third parties by or through the Site, if any, are not the responsibility of HouseCarers.com and are not subject to the TCU. Please contact the third party placing these cookies to find out what information is collected and how it is used. You can usually edit your browser not to accept cookies, but the features of our Site may not function properly if you do not accept cookies.   

 **5. How HouseCarers.com protects your personal information.**  
  
For all our transactions, we employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. Where appropriate, we password protect, use encryption techniques and install firewalls. We strive to protect you. We encourage our participating service providers to adopt and honor their own consumer privacy policies. For all our efforts to safeguard your privacy, no system can be guaranteed. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Once we receive your information, we use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.   

 **6. How you can access, update or delete your information. **  
  
As part of your use of the Site, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your membership Registration Data with current, accurate and complete information. You may view, update and/or edit the membership Data you have provided to HouseCarers.com by logging in to your account and following the appropriate instructions.   

 **7. What else you should know about your online privacy. **  
  
The Site may also contain links to other web sites and advertising. The privacy policies of those web sites and advertisers may significantly differ from that of our Site. It is your responsibility to contact such web site operator or advertiser directly to determine their privacy policy.   

 **8. How you can contact us.**  
  
Any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site should be directed to:   
Customer Service  
HouseCarers.com   
PO Box 404 Belmont  
NSW 2280  
 Australia

Click here to contact housecarers 

Top
